icdlarabia.org 2018-10-12

# Privacy Policy - ICDL Arabia

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

**What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app? & When do we collect information?**

Self-registration is not available in our systems, ICDL Arabia is collecting the information during the accreditation process where a form will be filled out by a center's authorized person with your center name, contact person, email address, phone number and other details.

**How do we use your information?**

  * To improve our website in order to better serve you.
  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To quickly process your transactions.
  * To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.
  * To follow up with them after correspondence (email or phone inquiries).

**How do we protect your information?**

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

**Do we use 'cookies'?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**We use cookies to:**

Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you turn cookies off, some features will be disabled. It won't affect the user's experience that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly.

However, you will still be able to place orders.

**Third-party disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information.

**Third-party links**

We do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.

**Google**

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

**COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States' consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.

**CAN SPAM Act**

ICDL Arabia abides by the regulations set for commercial email. By law, any commercial email sent by ICDL Arabia will give recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them.

**We collect  email addresses in order to:**

      • Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions

      • Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.

      • Send you additional information related to your product and/or service

      • Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.

**We also agree to the following:**

      • Not to use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.

      • Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.

      • Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.

      • Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.

      • Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.

      • Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

**If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at info@icdlarabia.org  ** **or Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.** **  We will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.**

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

icdlarabia.org  
Dubai,  
United Arab Emirates  
+971 4 4540 420

**Last Edited DATE : Sep 07, 2017**
